var questions=[ 
    {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",

    answers: [
        "JavaScript is a lightweight, interpreted programming language.",

        "JavaScript is designed for creating network-centric applications.",

        "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java.",

        "All of the above.",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Which of the following type of variable is visible everywhere in your JavaScript code?",

    answers: [
        "global variable",
        "local variable",
        "Both of the above.",
        " None of the above.",
    ],
    answer: 0,
},
{
    question: " Which built-in method returns the length of the string?",

    answers: [
        "A - length()",
        "B - size()",
        "C - index()",
        "D - None of the above.",
    ],

    answer: 0,
},
{
    question: "Which of the following function of Number object forces a number to display in exponential notation?",

    answers: [
        "A - toExponential()",
        "B - toFixed()",
        "C - toPrecision()",
        "D - toLocaleString()",
    ],

    answer: 0,
},
{
    question: "Which of the following function of Number object defines how many total digits to display of a number?",

    answers: [
        "A - toExponential()",
        "B - toFixed()",
        "C - toLocaleString()",
        "D - toPrecision()",
    ],

    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: " Which of the following function of String object executes the search for a match between a regular expression and a specified string?",

    answers: ["A - concat()", "B - match()", "C - replace()", "D - search()"],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Which of the following function of String object creates a string to be displayed in a big font as if it were in a <big> tag?",

    answers: ["A - anchor()", "B - big()", "C - blink()", "D - italics()"],

    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: 'Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed in the specified size as if it were in a <font size = "' +
        "size" +
        '"> tag?',

    answers: ["A - fixed()", "B - fontcolor()", "C - fontsize()", "D - bold()"],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Which of the following function of Array object removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",

    answers: ["A - pop()", "B - push()", "C - join()", "D - map()"],

    answer: 0,
},
{
    question: " Which of the following function of Array object sorts the elements of an array?",

    answers: [
        "A - toSource()",
        "B - sort()",
        "C - toString()",
        "D - unshift()",
    ],

    answer: 1,
}
]